<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:15:44 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E07 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e07-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:15:26 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E06 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e06-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:14:42 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E05 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e05-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:13:28 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E04 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e04-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:11:52 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E03 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e03-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:10:46 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E02 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e02-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:10:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E01 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e01-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:09:01 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Revenge - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-revenge-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Witches of Eastwick is a 1987 American dark fantasy comedy film directed by George Miller and based on John Updike&amp;#39;s 1984 novel of the same name. It stars Jack Nicholson alongside Cher, Michelle Pfeiffer, Susan Sarandon and Veronica Cartwright.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film follows three best friends who are unaware that they are witches and that their regular meetings have formed an informal coven; the arrival in town of a mysterious man who starts courting them marks the start of a back-and-forth between him and the three women.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:20:25 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Part 2 - The Other One - 2022</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-part-2-the-other-one-2022/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Witcher is a fantasy drama television series created by Lauren Schmidt Hissrich for Netflix. It is based on the book series[a] by Polish author Andrzej Sapkowski. Set on a fictional, medieval-inspired landmass known as the Continent, The Witcher explores the legend of Geralt of Rivia, Yennefer of Vengerberg and Princess Ciri. It stars Henry Cavill, Anya Chalotra, and Freya Allan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The first season, consisting of eight episodes, was released on Netflix on December 20, 2019. It was based on The Last Wish and Sword of Destiny, which are collections of short stories that precede the main The Witcher saga. The second season, also consisting of eight episodes and based on the novel Blood of Elves, was released on December 17, 2021. In September 2021, Netflix renewed the series for a third season, which also consists of eight episodes, released in two volumes on June 29 and July 27, 2023. This will be followed by a fourth season, with Liam Hemsworth taking over the role of Geralt of Rivia. In April 2024, the series was renewed for its fifth and final season.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:18:33 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Part 1 - The Subversion - 2018</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-part-1-the-subversion-2018/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Charmed is an American fantasy drama television series created by Constance M. Burge and produced by Aaron Spelling and his production company Spelling Television, with Brad Kern serving as showrunner. The series was originally broadcast by The WB from October 7, 1998, until May 21, 2006. The series narrative follows a trio of sisters, known as The Charmed Ones, the most-powerful, good witches of all time, who use their combined &amp;#34;Power of Three&amp;#34; to protect innocent lives from evil beings such as demons and warlocks. Each sister possesses unique magical powers that grow and evolve, while they attempt to maintain normal lives in modern-day San Francisco. Keeping their supernatural identities separate and secret from their ordinary lives often becomes a challenge for them, with the exposure of magic having far-reaching consequences on their various relationships and resulting in a number of police and FBI investigations throughout the series. The series initially focuses on the three Halliwell sisters, Prue (Shannen Doherty), Piper (Holly Marie Combs), and Phoebe (Alyssa Milano).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:15:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Jawan - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/jawan-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Jawan (/dʒəwɑːn/ transl. Soldier) is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language vigilante action film co-written and directed by Atlee (in his Hindi film debut).[5] It is produced by Gauri Khan and Gaurav Verma under Red Chillies Entertainment. The film stars Shah Rukh Khan in a dual role as a father and son alongside Nayanthara (in her Hindi film debut) and Vijay Sethupathi. In the film, Azad, the jailer of a woman&amp;#39;s prison and a vigilante who recruits inmates and commits acts that shed light on corruption in India.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:03:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fast and Furious Presents - Hobbs and Shaw - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fast-and-furious-presents-hobbs-and-shaw-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest-grossing action films of all time, sci-fi, superhero and fantasy films are not included; see List of highest-grossing science fiction films, List of highest-grossing superhero films and List of highest-grossing fantasy films.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest grossing action films of time. The top 3 are along the highest-grossing films, being 11th, 12th and 33rd. James Bond is the most frequent franchise with 11 films on the list. All of the films have had a theatrical run (including re-releases) since 1991, and films that have not played during this period do not appear on the chart because of ticket-price inflation, population size and ticket purchasing trends not being considered. 2015 is the most frequent year with 5 films on the list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:55:56 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Diljale - 1996</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/diljale-1996/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Diljale (transl. The burning heart) is a 1996 Indian Hindi-language romantic action film directed by Harry Baweja, with screenplay by Karan Razdan. The film stars Ajay Devgn, Madhoo and Sonali Bendre along with Parmeet Sethi, Shakti Kapoor, Gulshan Grover and Amrish Puri in supporting roles. The film received positive reviews, and earned a lifetime gross of ₹ 15.85 crore.[2] IBNLive included Diljale among its list of &amp;#34;Ajay Devgn&amp;#39;s memorable films&amp;#34;.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:54:05 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fast and Furious Presents - Hobbs &amp; Shaw - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fast-and-furious-presents-hobbs-shaw-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest-grossing action films of all time, sci-fi, superhero and fantasy films are not included; see List of highest-grossing science fiction films, List of highest-grossing superhero films and List of highest-grossing fantasy films.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest grossing action films of time. The top 3 are along the highest-grossing films, being 11th, 12th and 33rd. James Bond is the most frequent franchise with 11 films on the list. All of the films have had a theatrical run (including re-releases) since 1991, and films that have not played during this period do not appear on the chart because of ticket-price inflation, population size and ticket purchasing trends not being considered. 2015 is the most frequent year with 5 films on the list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:43:53 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>San Andreas - 2015</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/san-andreas-2015/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;San Andreas is a 2015 American disaster thriller film directed by Brad Peyton and written by Carlton Cuse, with Andre Fabrizio and Jeremy Passmore receiving story credit. The film stars Dwayne Johnson in the lead role, with Carla Gugino, Alexandra Daddario, Ioan Gruffudd, Archie Panjabi and Paul Giamatti. Its plot centers on a massive earthquake caused by the San Andreas Fault that devastates the West Coast of the United States.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:40:45 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fast X - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fast-x-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Jaane Jaan (transl.  Beloved), released internationally as Suspect X,[1] is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language mystery thriller film written and directed by Sujoy Ghosh.[2][3] The film is an adaptation of the 2005 Japanese novel The Devotion of Suspect X by Keigo Higashino, which had earlier been made into the 2012 South Korean film Perfect Number by Bang Eun-jin.[4][5][6] The film is produced under the banner 12th Street Entertainment and Northern Lights Films in association with Kross Pictures and Balaji Motion Pictures.[7] It stars Kareena Kapoor Khan as a single mother involved in a murder, alongside Jaideep Ahlawat and Vijay Varma.[8][9] It released on 21 September 2023 on Netflix,[10][11] to positive reviews from film critics, with particular praise directed towards the performances of the lead cast.[12]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:34:33 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>F9 - 2021</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/f9-2021/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Wicked (titled on-screen as Wicked: Part I) is a 2024 American musical fantasy film directed by Jon M. Chu and written by Winnie Holzman and Dana Fox. It adapts the first act of the 2003 stage musical by Stephen Schwartz and Holzman, which was loosely based on Gregory Maguire&amp;#39;s 1995 novel, itself a reimagining of L. Frank Baum&amp;#39;s The Wonderful Wizard of Oz and its 1939 film adaptation. The film stars Cynthia Erivo as Elphaba Thropp and Ariana Grande[b] as Galinda Upland, with Jonathan Bailey, Ethan Slater, Bowen Yang, Marissa Bode, Peter Dinklage, Michelle Yeoh, and Jeff Goldblum in supporting roles. Set in the Land of Oz before Dorothy Gale arrives from Kansas, its plot follows Elphaba, the future Wicked Witch of the West, and her friendship with her classmate Galinda, who becomes Glinda the Good.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:31:23 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fate of the Furious - 2017</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-fate-of-the-furious-2017/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Fate of the Furious: The Album is the soundtrack album to The Fate of the Furious. It was released on April 14, 2017, by Artist Partner Group and Atlantic Records, in conjunction of the film&amp;#39;s US theatrical release. It was promoted by six singles: &amp;#34;Go Off&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Hey Ma&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Good Life&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Gang Up&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Horses&amp;#34;, and &amp;#34;Candy Paint&amp;#34;.[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The first single of the album, &amp;#34;Go Off&amp;#34;, was released on March 2, 2017.[2] The song is performed by Lil Uzi Vert, Quavo and Travis Scott. The second single, &amp;#34;Hey Ma&amp;#34;, by Pitbull and J Balvin featuring Camila Cabello, was released on March 10.[3] &amp;#34;Good Life&amp;#34; by G-Eazy and Kehlani was released as the third single on March 17.[4] &amp;#34;Gang Up&amp;#34; by Young Thug, 2 Chainz, Wiz Khalifa and PnB Rock was released as the fourth single on March 24.[5] The fifth single, &amp;#34;Horses&amp;#34;, by PnB Rock, Kodak Black and A Boogie wit da Hoodie, was released on March 30.[6] The sixth single, &amp;#34;Candy Paint&amp;#34;, performed by Post Malone, was released on October 20.[7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:29:40 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Furious 7 - 2015</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/furious-7-2015/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Fast Five (also known as Fast &amp;amp; Furious 5) is a 2011 action film directed by Justin Lin and written by Chris Morgan. It is the sequel to Fast &amp;amp; Furious (2009) and the fifth installment in the Fast &amp;amp; Furious franchise. The film stars Vin Diesel as Dominic Toretto and Paul Walker as Brian O&amp;#39;Conner, alongside Jordana Brewster, Tyrese Gibson,
Gal Gadot, Chris &amp;#34;Ludacris&amp;#34; Bridges, Matt Schulze, Sung Kang and Dwayne Johnson. In the film, Dom and Brian, along with Dom&amp;#39;s sister Mia plan a heist to steal $100 million from corrupt businessman Hernan Reyes while being pursued for arrest by U.S. Diplomatic Security Service (DSS) agent Luke Hobbs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:21:02 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fast and Furious 6 - 2013</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fast-and-furious-6-2013/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Fast &amp;amp; Furious (also known as Fast &amp;amp; Furious 4) is a 2009 action film directed by Justin Lin and written by Chris Morgan. It is the direct sequel to The Fast and the Furious (2001) and 2 Fast 2 Furious (2003) as well as the fourth installment in the Fast &amp;amp; Furious franchise. It stars Vin Diesel, Paul Walker, Michelle Rodriguez, and Jordana Brewster. In the film, Dominic Toretto (Diesel) and FBI agent Brian O&amp;#39;Conner (Walker) are forced to work together to avenge the murder of Toretto&amp;#39;s lover Letty Ortiz (Rodriguez) and apprehend drug lord Arturo Braga (John Ortiz).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 07:17:45 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>