<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:27:17 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fikar Karo-Na - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fikar-karo-na-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Asha Bhosle is an Indian playback singer who has been cited by the Guinness Book of World Records as the most recorded singer in history.[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;| &amp;#34;Maang Ke Saath Tumhaara&amp;#34; -&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;| &amp;#34;Main Chali, Main Chali&amp;#34; -&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:21:45 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Deva - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/deva-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Deva is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language action thriller film directed by Rosshan Andrrews, and produced by Siddharth Roy Kapur under Roy Kapur Films. The film stars Shahid Kapoor, Pooja Hegde and Pavail Gulati. It is a remake of Andrrews&amp;#39;s own 2013 Malayalam film Mumbai Police, with a different climax.[5] The film follows a violent cop who undergoes a personality change after losing his memory in an accident and has to reinvestigate the murder of a fellow police officer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:16:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Umbarro- 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/umbarro-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Umbarro is a 2025 Gujarati family comedy drama film directed by Abhishek Shah. It stars Vandana Pathak, Kaajal Oza Vaidya, Suchita Trivedi, Deeksha Joshi, Tarjanee Bhadla, Tejal Panchasara, Vineeta Joshee, Aarjav Trivedi, and Galsar Sanjay in a lead role.[3] The film is a remake of 2021 Marathi film Jhimma.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Seven women from rural Gujarat embark on their first international trip to London, facing cultural clashes, language barriers, and societal stigmas along their journey to claim their space in the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:59:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuk-tuk - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/tuk-tuk-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Tuk Tuk is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language supernatural comedy film[1] written and directed by Supreeth C Krishna, produced by Rahul Reddy D, Lokku Sri Varun, C Sree Ramulu Reddy under the banners of Chitravaahani Producions and RYG Cinemas[2] The film features Harsh Roshan, Karthikeya Dev, Madhu Sudhan Rapeti, Saanve Megghana and Nihal Kodhaty in important roles.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;In a rural village of Chittoor, three aimless young men, desperate to earn money, resort to secretly recording women bathing. Their lives take a strange turn when they come across a scooter possessed by a spirit. Seizing the opportunity, they use the scooter to lead a Ganesh Chaturthi procession and start making money. However, their world is turned upside down when they discover the spirit is actually a girl. The rest of the story unravels the mystery of how the girl became a spirit, how she ended up in the scooter, and the tragic love story that led to her untimely fate.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:55:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mad Square - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mad-square-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mad Square (stylized as MAD²) is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language action comedy film written and directed by Kalyan Shankar and produced by Haarika Suryadevara and S. Naga Vamsi. A sequel to the 2023 film Mad, the film has an ensemble cast of Narne Nithiin, Sangeeth Sobhan, Ram Nitin and Priyanka Jawalkar.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released on 28 March 2025[4][5] to mixed reviews from critics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:51:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Ash - 2025 ( Hindi-English )</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/ash-2025-hindi-english/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;This is a list of Hindi cinema films released in 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is the list of highest-grossing Hindi cinema films released in 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:46:17 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Emergency - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/emergency-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Emergency is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language historical biographical drama film[7] directed and co-produced by Kangana Ranaut, based on a screenplay by Ritesh Shah and story written by Ranaut.[8] Based on the Indian Emergency, it stars Ranaut as former Prime Minister of India, Indira Gandhi.[9][10]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Principal photography commenced in July 2022 and ended in January 2023.[11] It was originally scheduled for release on 6 September 2024, but was postponed due to pending certification of the Central Board of Film Certification.[12][13] Later, it was cleared by CBFC and released on 17 January 2025 to negative reviews from film critics.[14][15][16] The film also emerged as a box-office flop.[17][18][19]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:06:09 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Nadaaniyan</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/nadaaniyan/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Nadaaniyan (transl. Innocence) is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language teen romantic comedy film directed by Shauna Gautam (in her directorial debut) and produced by Karan Johar, Apoorva Mehta and Somen Mishra under Dharmatic Entertainment. The film stars Ibrahim Ali Khan (in his acting debut) and Khushi Kapoor, alongside Mahima Chaudhry, Dia Mirza, Suniel Shetty, and Jugal Hansraj. It tells the story of a privileged South Delhi school girl who gets a boyfriend-for-hire to get back at her family and classmates.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:31:49 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Dil Dosti Aur Dogs - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/dil-dosti-aur-dogs-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;This is a list of Hindi language films produced in Bollywood in India that are scheduled to be released in the year 2025.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is the list of highest-grossing Hindi cinema films released in 2025.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:22:06 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Legally Veer - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/legally-veer-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Wicked (titled on-screen as Wicked: Part I) is a 2024 American musical fantasy film directed by Jon M. Chu and written by Winnie Holzman and Dana Fox. It adapts the first act of the 2003 stage musical by Stephen Schwartz and Holzman, which was loosely based on Gregory Maguire&amp;#39;s 1995 novel, itself a reimagining of L. Frank Baum&amp;#39;s The Wonderful Wizard of Oz and its 1939 film adaptation. The film stars Cynthia Erivo as Elphaba Thropp and Ariana Grande[b] as Galinda Upland, with Jonathan Bailey, Ethan Slater, Bowen Yang, Marissa Bode, Peter Dinklage, Michelle Yeoh, and Jeff Goldblum in supporting roles. Set in the Land of Oz before Dorothy Gale arrives from Kansas, its plot follows Elphaba, the future Wicked Witch of the West, and her friendship with her classmate Galinda, who becomes Glinda the Good.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:11:04 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaat - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/jaat-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Jaat is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language action film written and directed by Gopichand Malineni (in his Hindi film debut), and produced by Mythri Movie Makers and People Media Factory.[5][6] The film stars Sunny Deol, Randeep Hooda and Regina Cassandra in lead roles alongside Saiyami Kher, Jagapathi Babu, Ramya Krishnan, Vineet Kumar Singh, Prashant Bajaj, Zarina Wahab, P. Ravi Shankar and Babloo Prithiveeraj.[7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Jaat follows a mysterious passenger whose obsessive demand for an apology brings him face-to-face with a ruthless labourer-turned-crime boss, resulting in a battle between the two.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:58:25 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Game Changer - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/game-changer-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Game Changer is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language political action drama film directed by S. Shankar, in his Telugu debut, and produced by Dil Raju under Sri Venkateswara Creations. The film stars Ram Charan in dual roles, alongside Kiara Advani, Anjali, S. J. Suryah, Srikanth, Sunil, Jayaram and Samuthirakani.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was officially announced in February 2021, with its title revealed in March 2023. Principal photography began in October 2021 and wrapped in July 2024, following multiple production delays. Filming took place across various locations in India, as well as international destinations including Japan, China, Malaysia, Cambodia and New Zealand. The film has music composed by Thaman S, cinematography handled by Tirru and editing by Shameer Muhammed and Ruben.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:49:26 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Laila Majnu - 1976</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/laila-majnu-1976/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Laila Majnu is a 1976 Indian Hindustani-language romantic drama film directed by Harnam Singh Rawail and starring Rishi Kapoor, Ranjeeta and Danny Denzongpa in lead roles. The film&amp;#39;s music is by Madan Mohan and Jaidev. Based on the legend of Layla and Majnun, it tells the story of two star-crossed lovers: Laila, a princess and Qais a.k.a. Majnu, a common man.[1][2][3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Laila Majnu marked the debut of Ranjeeta. Upon its release in 1976, it garnered highly positive reviews from film critics, and became a box-office success. The humongous success of the film cemented Rishi Kapoor&amp;#39;s status as a bankable star; for after his debut in Bobby (1973), he did not have any major success before Laila Majnu, with the exception of Kabhi Kabhie (1976). However, the success of that film was credited towards Shashi Kapoor and Amitabh Bachchan. Since its release in 1976, Laila Majnu is hailed as a cult classic.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:41:31 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Sivappu Manjal Pachai - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/sivappu-manjal-pachai-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Sivappu Manjal Pachai (transl. Red, yellow, green) is a 2019 Indian Tamil-language action thriller film written and directed by Sasi. The film stars Siddharth, G. V. Prakash Kumar, Lijomol Jose, and Kashmira Pardeshi, and marks the Tamil film debuts of both Lijomol and Pardeshi. The film is produced by Ramesh P. Pillai under the banner of Abhishek Films. Principal photography of the film commenced in July 2018.[1] The film was released on 6 September 2019 to positive reviews and become a hit at the box office.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:35:44 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Reddy - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/love-reddy-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pushpa 2: The Rule is a 2024 Indian Telugu-language action drama film[8] written and directed by Sukumar and produced by Mythri Movie Makers in association with Sukumar Writings. A sequel to Pushpa: The Rise (2021), it is the second installment in the Pushpa film series. The film stars Allu Arjun in the titular role, alongside Rashmika Mandanna, Fahadh Faasil, Jagapathi Babu, Sunil, and Rao Ramesh. It follows Pushpa Raj, a labourer-turned-red sandalwood smuggler, as he faces growing threats from his enemies, including SP Bhanwar Singh Shekhawat.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:28:28 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Badass Ravikumar - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/badass-ravikumar-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Badass Ravi Kumar is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language musical action film[5] directed by Keith Gomes in his feature film directorial debut and produced by Himesh Reshammiya Melodies. It is a spin off film of the 2014 film The Xpose and the second installment in The Xposé Universe, with Himesh Reshammiya reprising his role as Ravi Kumar, while Prabhu Deva, Kirti Kulhari, Simona J, Saurabh Sachdeva, Sanjay Mishra, and Johnny Lever appear in supporting roles.[6][7][8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:21:31 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Hera Pheri - 2000</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/hera-pheri-2000/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Hera Pheri (transl. Foul Play) is a 2000 Indian Hindi-language heist comedy drama film directed by Priyadarshan and written by Neeraj Vora, starring Akshay Kumar, Suniel Shetty, Paresh Rawal, Tabu, Om Puri and Gulshan Grover.[4] The film is a remake of 1989 Malayalam film Ramji Rao Speaking which itself was inspired by the 1971 American TV movie See The Man Run.[5][6][7] It is the first instalment of the Hera Pheri franchise. The plot revolves around two tenants, Raju and Shyam, and their landlord, Baburao Ganpatrao Apte, who are in desperate need of money. They chance upon a ransom call through a cross-connection and hatch a plan to claim the ransom for themselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:57:01 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Diplomat - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-diplomat-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Diplomat is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language political thriller film directed by Shivam Nair and written by Ritesh Shah.[6] The film, starring John Abraham and Sadia Khateeb, is set against the backdrop of India–Pakistan relations, exploring themes of diplomacy and the personal conflicts faced by diplomats.[7][8]
It was theatrically released during the Holi festival on 14 March 2025 with highly positive reviews and achieved significant commercial success. It grossed ₹54 crores worldwide, with India contributing ₹41 crores net to the total earnings. Notably, the film&amp;amp;rsquo;s production budget was ₹20 crores, making it a profitable venture..[9] The movie is based on the real-life case of Uzma Ahmed, who returned to India in 2017.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:54:56 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Siddharth Roy - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/siddharth-roy-2024/</link><description>
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 mx-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags: siddharth roy 2024,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed,siddharth roy 2024 movie download filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 mmsub,siddharth roy net worth,siddharth roy kapur upcoming movies,siddharth roy kapur age,siddharth roy cbfc a 2024 romance,siddharth roy 2024 bangla subtitle,siddharth roy kapur son,siddharth roy 2024 cast,siddharth roy 2024 movie cast,siddharth roy kapur net worth,siddharth roy 2024 download in hindi,siddharth roy 2024 download in hindi filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 dual audio hindi,siddharth roy 2024 download filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 release date,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed movie download,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed download,siddharth roy 2024 english sub,siddharth roy 2024 full movie,siddharth roy 2024 full movie download,siddharth roy 2024 film,siddharth roy 2024 filmyzilla download,siddharth roy 2024 filmywap,siddharth roy movie 2024 filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 hindi,siddharth roy 2024 hindi movie,siddharth roy 2024 hit or flop,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed watch online,siddharth roy.2024.hdrip,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 hindi dubbed full movie,siddharth roy 2024 imdb,siddharth roy 2024 in hindi,siddharth roy movie 2024 in hindi dubbed,siddharth roy movie 2024 in telugu,index of siddharth roy (2024),ibomma 2024 siddharth roy,siddharth roy 2024 language,siddharth roy 2024 movie,siddharth roy 2024 movie hindi dubbed download,siddharth roy 2024 movie sinhala subtitles download,siddharth roy 2024 movie hindi dubbed,siddharth roy 2024 movie watch online,siddharth roy 2024 movie download in hindi filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 movie hindi dubbed filmyzilla,siddharth roy 2024 movie filmyzilla,siddharth roy movie name 2024,siddharth roy 2024 ott release date,siddharth roy 2024 ott,siddharth roy (2024) online,siddharth roy 2024 ott platform,siddharth roy 2024 movie online,siddharth roy 2024 poster,siddharth roy 2024 movie poster,siddharth roy 2024 review,siddharth roy 2024 rating,siddharth roy 2024 remake,siddharth roy 2024 movie release date,siddharth roy cbfc a 2024 ‧ romance/drama,siddharth roy 2024 sinhala,siddharth roy 2024 sinhala sub watch online,siddharth roy 2024 sub,siddharth roy 2024 south movie,siddharth roy 2024 telugu,siddharth roy 2024 trailer,siddharth roy 2024 telugu movie,siddharth roy 2024 tamil,siddharth roy 2024 tamil movie download,siddharth roy 2024 telugu sinhala sub,siddharth roy trailer movie 2024,siddharth roy tamil movie 2024,siddharth roy 2024 vegamovies,siddharth roy 2024 watch online,siddharth roy 2024 wikipedia,siddharth roy 2024 wiki,watch siddharth roy 2024
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:27:13 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanam teri kasam 2016</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/sanam-teri-kasam-2016/</link><description>
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 mx-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags: sanam teri kasam 2016,sanam teri kasam 2016 cast,sanam teri kasam 2016 film,sanam teri kasam 2016 hindi,sanam teri kasam 2016 imdb,sanam teri kasam 2016 movie,sanam teri kasam 2016 mmsub,sanam teri kasam 2016 mp3 download,sanam teri kasam 2016.mp4moviez,sanam teri kasam 2016 movie download pagalworld,sanam teri kasam 2016 movie download filmyzilla,sanam teri kasam 2016 movie download mp4moviez,sanam teri kasam full movie 2016,sanam teri kasam 2016 ott,pemain sanam teri kasam 2016,sanam teri kasam 2016 songs,sanam teri kasam 2016 trailer,sanam teri kasam 2016 wiki,sanam teri kasam 2016 wikipedia,sanam teri kasam 2016 songs wynk music,sanam teri kasam 2016 full movie download,sanam teri kasam 2016 sinhala subtitles download
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:43:18 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>