<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:43:10 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Bhog - 2025 Season 1 Complete EP01-06</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/bhog-2025-season-1-complete-ep01-06/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mohanlal is an Indian actor, producer, distributor, host, and playback singer who has starred in mainstream blockbuster and art-house films.[1] He has made over 360 appearances in feature films during the span of his career, primarily in Malayalam cinema and also in Tamil, Telugu, Hindi and Kannada films.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mohanlal began acting at the age of 18 in a brief role in the then-unreleased film Thiranottam (1978), released a quarter century later. He made his cinematic debut in 1980 as an antagonist in the romantic thriller Manjil Virinja Pookkal.[3] His portrayal of Narendran, a sadistic husband, garnered him recognition and the film developed a cult status.[4][5] He was thereafter cast in several films as villainous characters. Padayottam (1982), the first Malayalam film shot on 70 mm film featured him in his first protagonistic role.[4] The family drama Aattakalasam established him as a leading actor in Malayalam cinema.[6] In 1984 he starred in the screwball comedy Poochakkoru Mookkuthi, whose success generated a trend and popularised the genre in the 1980s.[7][8] He played an antihero in Uyarangalil (1984), directed by I. V. Sasi receiving critical acclaim for his performance.[9] In the same year, he co-founded Casino Films,[a] a motion picture production company that later produced his comedy films Gandhinagar 2nd Street (1986) and Nadodikkattu (1987).[10]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 18:07:04 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Chhaava - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/chhaava-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Diplomat is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language political thriller film directed by Shivam Nair and written by Ritesh Shah.[6] The film, starring John Abraham and Sadia Khateeb, is set against the backdrop of India–Pakistan relations, exploring themes of diplomacy and the personal conflicts faced by diplomats.[7][8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Diplomat was theatrically released during the Holi festival on 14 March 2025 with highly positive reviews and achieved significant commercial success. The film grossed over ₹53 crore worldwide. It is based on the real-life case of Uzma Ahmed, who returned to India in 2017.[9]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:34:33 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Run - 2004</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/run-2004/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Run is a 2004 Indian Hindi-language romantic action film directed and photographed by Jeeva. It stars Abhishek Bachchan and Bhumika Chawla.[1][2] It is a remake of a 2002 Tamil film of the same name for which Jeeva worked as a cinematographer. The film was produced by Boney Kapoor and Sridevi under the banner Sridevi Productions.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Siddharth alias &amp;#34;Sidhu&amp;#34; comes to New Delhi for his further studies and stays with his sister Esha from Allahabad. His spoiled friend Ganesh trails behind him and arrives later. Sidhu, through perceived destiny and chance, bumps into Janhvi and falls in love with her. Janhvi belongs to a conservative Haryanvi family where her elder brother, Ganpat, is the head and is very protective of his family, mainly his sister, after the loss of their parents.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:23:26 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Pirates of the Caribbean - Dead Men Tell No Tales - 2017</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-men-tell-no-tales-2017/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pirates of the Caribbean is an American fantasy supernatural swashbuckler film series produced by Jerry Bruckheimer and based on Walt Disney&amp;#39;s theme park attraction of the same name. The film series serves as a major component of the titular media franchise. The films&amp;#39; plots are set primarily in the Caribbean, based on a fictionalized version of the Golden Age of Piracy (c. 1650–1726) while also leading to the range of a mid-1700s setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:17:47 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Pirates of the Caribbean - On Stranger Tides - 2011</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-on-stranger-tides-2011/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pirates of the Caribbean is an American fantasy supernatural swashbuckler film series produced by Jerry Bruckheimer and based on Walt Disney&amp;#39;s theme park attraction of the same name. The film series serves as a major component of the titular media franchise. The films&amp;#39; plots are set primarily in the Caribbean, based on a fictionalized version of the Golden Age of Piracy (c. 1650–1726) while also leading to the range of a mid-1700s setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:52:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End - 2007</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-world-s-end-2007/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pirates of the Caribbean is a dark ride at Disneyland, Walt Disney World&amp;#39;s Magic Kingdom, Tokyo Disneyland and Disneyland Park at Disneyland Paris.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The ride tells the story of a band of pirates in the West Indies islands around the Caribbean Sea in the 17th and 18th centuries with the saga of their voyages, troubles, and exploits. The original version of the ride opened at the Disneyland in Anaheim, California, near Los Angeles, in 1967, and was the last ride whose construction was envisioned and personally overseen by Walt Disney, who died three months before it opened. After immense popularity, the ride was replicated six years later at the Magic Kingdom of Walt Disney World, near Orlando, Florida in 1973. Versions followed at Tokyo Disneyland in 1983, and at Disneyland Paris in 1992. Each of the initial four versions of the ride has a different façade but a similar ride experience.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:45:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Pirates of the Caribbean - Dead Man's Chest - 2006</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-dead-man-s-chest-2006/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pirates of the Caribbean is a dark ride at Disneyland, Walt Disney World&amp;#39;s Magic Kingdom, Tokyo Disneyland and Disneyland Park at Disneyland Paris.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The ride tells the story of a band of pirates in the West Indies islands around the Caribbean Sea in the 17th and 18th centuries with the saga of their voyages, troubles, and exploits. The original version of the ride opened at the Disneyland in Anaheim, California, near Los Angeles, in 1967, and was the last ride whose construction was envisioned and personally overseen by Walt Disney, who died three months before it opened. After immense popularity, the ride was replicated six years later at the Magic Kingdom of Walt Disney World, near Orlando, Florida in 1973. Versions followed at Tokyo Disneyland in 1983, and at Disneyland Paris in 1992. Each of the initial four versions of the ride has a different façade but a similar ride experience.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:09:22 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Pirates of the Caribbean - The Curse of the Black Pearl - 2003</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/pirates-of-the-caribbean-the-curse-of-the-black-pearl-2003/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Pirates of the Caribbean is an American fantasy supernatural swashbuckler film series produced by Jerry Bruckheimer and based on Walt Disney&amp;#39;s theme park attraction of the same name. The film series serves as a major component of the titular media franchise. The films&amp;#39; plots are set primarily in the Caribbean, based on a fictionalized version of the Golden Age of Piracy (c. 1650–1726) while also leading to the range of a mid-1700s setting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:05:28 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Saand Ki Aankh - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/saand-ki-aankh-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Saand Ki Aankh (transl. Bull&amp;#39;s eye) is a 2019 Indian biographical drama film directed by Tushar Hiranandani and produced by Anurag Kashyap, Reliance Entertainment and Nidhi Parmar.[4][5][6] The film stars Taapsee Pannu, Bhumi Pednekar, Prakash Jha, and Vineet Kumar Singh. It highlights the lives of sharpshooters Chandro and Prakashi Tomar.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Filming began in February 2019 at Baghpat, with principal photography also held in Hastinapur and Mawana.[7] The film was released on 25 October 2019, coinciding with the Diwali festival.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 11:00:58 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Humraaz - 2002</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/humraaz-2002/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Aitraaz (transl. Objection) is a 2004 Indian Hindi-language romantic thriller film directed by Abbas–Mustan and produced by Subhash Ghai. It stars Akshay Kumar, Priyanka Chopra and Kareena Kapoor.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Aitraaz tells the story of a man accused of sexual harassment by his female superior, and was released on 12 November 2004 to positive reviews. Chopra received widespread critical acclaim for her performance. Loosely based on the 1994 film Disclosure,[3] the film was a major commercial success grossing ₹260 million at the box office against a budget of ₹110 million, and has been noted for its bold subject of male sexual harassment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:58:44 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lord of the Rings - The Two Towers - 2002</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-two-towers-2002/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;There are many video games that have been inspired by J. R. R. Tolkien&amp;#39;s works set in Middle-earth. Titles have been produced by studios such as Electronic Arts, Vivendi Games, Melbourne House, and Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment.[1][2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;In 1982, Melbourne House began a series of licensed Lord of the Rings graphical interactive fiction (text adventure) games with The Hobbit, based on the book with the same name.[3] The game was considered quite advanced at the time, with interactive characters that moved between locations independent of the player, and Melbourne House&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Inglish&amp;#39; text parser which accepted full-sentence commands where the norm was simple two-word verb/noun commands.[4][5] They went on to release 1986&amp;#39;s The Fellowship of the Ring, 1987&amp;#39;s Shadows of Mordor, and 1989&amp;#39;s The Crack of Doom.
A BBC Micro text adventure released around the same time was unrelated to Melbourne&amp;#39;s titles except for the literary origin.
In 1987, Melbourne House released War in Middle Earth, a real-time strategy game.[6][7]
Konami also released an action-strategy game titled J. R. R. Tolkien&amp;#39;s Riders of Rohan.[8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:56:01 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Rautu Ka Raaz - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/rautu-ka-raaz-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Rautu Ka Raaz is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language mystery film directed by Anand Surapur and produced by Zee Studios along with Umesh Kr Bansal, Anand Surapur and Chintu Srivastava. The film stars Nawazuddin Siddiqui, Narayani Shastri, Rajesh Kumar and Atul Tiwari in key roles.[1][2][3] It was featured at the 54th IFFI.[4][5]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;It was released over ZEE5 on 28 June 2024 to positive reviews.[6][7][8][9][10][11]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:53:18 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Valiant One - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/valiant-one-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mark Antony is a 2023 Indian Tamil-language science fiction action comedy film directed by Adhik Ravichandran. The film stars Vishal and S. J. Suryah in dual roles with Ritu Varma, Sunil, Selvaraghavan, Abhinaya, Y. G. Mahendran, Nizhalgal Ravi, Redin Kingsley and Manikandan in supporting roles. In the film, Mark, the son of a gangster Antony, finds a telephone which can contact the past, but Madhan, the son of rival gangster Jackie, wants it for himself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:49:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bayou - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-bayou-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The music for the 2025 period supernatural horror film Sinners written, produced, and directed by Ryan Coogler, consisted of two projects produced by Sony Music. The first album, Sinners (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack), featured various genres performed by blues musicians along with the cast members. The second album, Sinners (Original Motion Picture Score), consisted of the original score composed by Ludwig Göransson, Coogler&amp;#39;s frequent collaborator. Both albums were distributed under the Sony Masterworks and Sony Classical Records labels on April 18, 2025, the same day as the film&amp;#39;s release.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:46:56 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympus Has Fallen - 2013</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/olympus-has-fallen-2013/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Olympus Has Fallen is a 2013 American political action thriller film directed and co-produced by Antoine Fuqua from a screenplay written by Creighton Rothenberger and Katrin Benedikt, and is the first installment in the Has Fallen film series. The film stars Gerard Butler (who also co-produced), Aaron Eckhart, and Morgan Freeman with Angela Bassett, Robert Forster, Cole Hauser, Ashley Judd, Melissa Leo, Dylan McDermott, Radha Mitchell, and Rick Yune in supporting roles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:44:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Free Guy - 2021</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/free-guy-2021/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Respect is a 2021 American biographical musical drama film directed by Liesl Tommy (in her feature directorial debut), written by Tracey Scott Wilson and Callie Khouri, based on the life of American singer Aretha Franklin. The film stars Jennifer Hudson as Franklin, with Forest Whitaker, Marlon Wayans, Audra McDonald, Marc Maron, Tituss Burgess, and Mary J. Blige in supporting roles. The film follows the first three decades of Franklin&amp;#39;s life, from being born as a musical prodigy in an affluent African-American family, the repercussions of losing her mother at age 10 to her arduous rise to international musical stardom, while enduring an abusive marriage, ultimately concluding with the recording of her influential live album Amazing Grace (1972).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:40:14 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mission Raniganj - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mission-raniganj-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mission Raniganj: The Great Bharat Rescue is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language disaster thriller film[4] directed by Tinu Suresh Desai and produced by Pooja Entertainment.[5][6] Based on the Raniganj Coalfields collapse of 1989 in West Bengal, the film stars Akshay Kumar and Parineeti Chopra.[7][8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mission Raniganj is based on Jaswant Singh Gill, a brave and diligent mining engineer from IIT Dhanbad who rescued 65 trapped miners at the Raniganj Coalfields in 1989.[9]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:57:19 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Avengers Grimm - 2015</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/avengers-grimm-2015/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Avengers Grimm is a 2015 American superhero film written, co-edited, and directed by Jeremy M. Inman. The film, produced by B-movie film company The Asylum, stars Casper Van Dien, Lou Ferrigno, Kimo Leopoldo, Lauren Parkinson, Milynn Sarley, Marah Fairclough, Rileah Vanderbilt, and Elizabeth Peterson.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film is a mockbuster of the Marvel Studios superhero film Avengers: Age of Ultron and the ABC TV series Once Upon a Time.[2] The film received negative reviews from critics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:47:17 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Aitraaz - 2004</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/aitraaz-2004/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mughal-e-Azam (transl. The Great Mughal) is a 1960 Indian epic historical drama film produced and directed by K. Asif. Starring Prithviraj Kapoor, Dilip Kumar, Madhubala, and Durga Khote, it follows the love affair between Mughal Prince Salim (who went on to become Emperor Jahangir) and Anarkali, a court dancer. Salim&amp;#39;s father, Emperor Akbar, disapproves of the relationship, which leads to a war between father and son.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:43:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Raid 2 - 2014</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-raid-2-2014/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Raid is a 2011 Indonesian action thriller film written and directed by Gareth Evans and produced by Ario Sagantoro.[6] The film stars Iko Uwais, Joe Taslim, Donny Alamsyah, Ray Sahetapy and Yayan Ruhian. The film follows an Indonesian National Police tactical squad that is deployed to raid a ruthless drug lord&amp;#39;s apartment block in the slums of Jakarta, only to be encircled by the criminals, forcing them to fight their way through the complex.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:37:06 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>