<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:01:22 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Lucky Baskhar - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/lucky-baskhar-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Lucky Baskhar (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) is the soundtrack album to the 2024 Telugu-language period crime drama film of the same name directed by Venky Atluri and produced by Suryadevara Naga Vamsi and Sai Soujanya under Sithara Entertainments, Srikara Studios and Fortune Four Cinemas, starring Dulquer Salmaan and Meenakshi Chaudhary. The album featured three songs composed by G. V. Prakash Kumar with lyrics written by Sri Mani and Ramajogayya Sastry. The album was released under the Aditya Music label on 11 November 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:55:43 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohrey - 2024 Season 1 Complete EP01 - EP08</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mohrey-2024-season-1-complete-ep01-ep08/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:15:58 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Exhuma - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/exhuma-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Shambhala is a 2024 drama film directed by Min Bahadur Bham from a screenplay written by Bham and Abinash Bikram Shah. Starring Thinley Lhamo, Tenzin Dalha and Sonam Topden.[1][2][3] Shambhala is the most expensive movie of Nepal made on the budget रू15 crore (US$1.1 million). It was selected in the Competition at the 74th Berlin International Film Festival, where it competed for the Golden Bear. The film narrates the life trajectory of a Tibetan female refugee who is feeling the brunt in search of her missing husband, a task which she has to do it amidst being pregnant under challenging precarious circumstances.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:07:53 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Seal Team Six - The Raid on Osama Bin Laden - 2012</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/seal-team-six-the-raid-on-osama-bin-laden-2012/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;On May 2,[a] 2011, the United States conducted Operation Neptune Spear, in which SEAL Team Six shot and killed Osama bin Laden at his &amp;#34;Waziristan Haveli&amp;#34; in Abbottabad, Pakistan.[1] Bin Laden, who founded al-Qaeda and masterminded the September 11 attacks, had been the subject of a United States military manhunt since the beginning of the War in Afghanistan, but escaped to Pakistan—allegedly with Pakistani support—during or after the Battle of Tora Bora in December 2001. The mission was part of an effort led by the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), with the Joint Special Operations Command (JSOC) coordinating the Special Mission Units involved in the raid. In addition to SEAL Team Six, participating units under JSOC included the 160th Special Operations Aviation Regiment (Airborne) and the CIA&amp;#39;s Special Activities Division, which recruits heavily from among former JSOC Special Mission Units.[2][3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:22:13 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Salaar Part 1 – Ceasefire - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/salaar-part-1-ceasefire-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;This is a list of Indian cinema films released in 2023.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is the list of highest-grossing Indian films released in 2023. The rank of the films in the following table depends on the estimate of worldwide collections as reported by organizations classified as green by Wikipedia.[a] There is no official tracking of domestic box office figures within India.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:16:45 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Interest</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/personal-interest/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The second season of the American television series Person of Interest premiered on September 27, 2012, on CBS and ended on May 9, 2013. The season is produced by Kilter Films, Bad Robot, and Warner Bros. Television, with Jonathan Nolan, Greg Plageman, J. J. Abrams, and Bryan Burk serving as executive producers and Plageman serving as showrunner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The series was renewed for a second season in March 2012[1] and stars Jim Caviezel, Taraji P. Henson, Kevin Chapman and Michael Emerson. The series revolves around a mysterious reclusive billionaire computer programmer, Harold Finch, who has developed a computer program for the federal government known as &amp;#34;the Machine&amp;#34; that is capable of collating all sources of information to predict terrorist acts and to identify people planning them. The Machine also identifies perpetrators and victims of other premeditated deadly crimes; however, because the government considers these &amp;#34;irrelevant&amp;#34;, Finch programs the Machine to delete this information each night and programs the Machine to notify him secretly of the &amp;#34;irrelevant&amp;#34; numbers. Finch recruits John Reese, a former Green Beret and CIA agent, now presumed dead – to investigate the people identified by the numbers the Machine has provided, and to act accordingly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:35:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Shaitaan - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/shaitaan-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Shaitaan (transl. Devil) is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language supernatural horror film directed by Vikas Bahl and produced by Devgn Films, Jio Studios, and Panorama Studios.[5] It stars Ajay Devgn, R. Madhavan, Jyothika, Janki Bodiwala, and Anngad Raaj.[6][7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;An adaptation of the 2023 Gujarati film Vash which also starred Bodiwala, Shaitaan revolves around a family which finds trouble when their daughter falls under the spell of black magic cast by a stranger, and they set out to stop the possession and uncover the stranger&amp;#39;s motives. The film was officially announced in May 2023, and entirely shot within the next three months in Dehradun and London.[8] This is Jyothika&amp;#39;s comeback to Bollywood since her debut film Doli Saja Ke Rakhna (1998).[8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:30:01 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Merry Christmas - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/merry-christmas-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Merry Christmas is a 2024 Indian mystery thriller film directed by Sriram Raghavan and produced by Tips Films together with Matchbox Pictures. The film, a Hindi-Tamil bilingual, stars Katrina Kaif and Vijay Sethupathi, alongside Ashwini Kalsekar, Luke Kenny, and Pari Maheshwari Sharma . The basic plot of the film was based on Frédéric Dard&amp;#39;s French novel Le Monte-charge (Bird in a Cage).[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was officially announced in December 2021. Principal photography commenced the same month in Mumbai along with a sporadic schedule in Uttar Pradesh, which was again followed with a schedule in the former location, and wrapped by mid-January 2023. The film has music composed by Pritam, cinematography handled by Madhu Neelakandan and editing by Pooja Ladha Surti.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:22:24 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E07 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e07-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:15:26 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E06 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e06-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:14:42 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E05 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e05-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:13:28 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E04 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e04-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:11:52 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E03 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e03-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:10:46 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E02 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e02-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:10:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Khakee The Bengal Chapter - S01 E01 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/khakee-the-bengal-chapter-s01-e01-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 05:09:01 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Revenge - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-revenge-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Witches of Eastwick is a 1987 American dark fantasy comedy film directed by George Miller and based on John Updike&amp;#39;s 1984 novel of the same name. It stars Jack Nicholson alongside Cher, Michelle Pfeiffer, Susan Sarandon and Veronica Cartwright.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film follows three best friends who are unaware that they are witches and that their regular meetings have formed an informal coven; the arrival in town of a mysterious man who starts courting them marks the start of a back-and-forth between him and the three women.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:20:25 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Part 2 - The Other One - 2022</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-part-2-the-other-one-2022/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Witcher is a fantasy drama television series created by Lauren Schmidt Hissrich for Netflix. It is based on the book series[a] by Polish author Andrzej Sapkowski. Set on a fictional, medieval-inspired landmass known as the Continent, The Witcher explores the legend of Geralt of Rivia, Yennefer of Vengerberg and Princess Ciri. It stars Henry Cavill, Anya Chalotra, and Freya Allan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The first season, consisting of eight episodes, was released on Netflix on December 20, 2019. It was based on The Last Wish and Sword of Destiny, which are collections of short stories that precede the main The Witcher saga. The second season, also consisting of eight episodes and based on the novel Blood of Elves, was released on December 17, 2021. In September 2021, Netflix renewed the series for a third season, which also consists of eight episodes, released in two volumes on June 29 and July 27, 2023. This will be followed by a fourth season, with Liam Hemsworth taking over the role of Geralt of Rivia. In April 2024, the series was renewed for its fifth and final season.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:18:33 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Witch Part 1 - The Subversion - 2018</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-witch-part-1-the-subversion-2018/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Charmed is an American fantasy drama television series created by Constance M. Burge and produced by Aaron Spelling and his production company Spelling Television, with Brad Kern serving as showrunner. The series was originally broadcast by The WB from October 7, 1998, until May 21, 2006. The series narrative follows a trio of sisters, known as The Charmed Ones, the most-powerful, good witches of all time, who use their combined &amp;#34;Power of Three&amp;#34; to protect innocent lives from evil beings such as demons and warlocks. Each sister possesses unique magical powers that grow and evolve, while they attempt to maintain normal lives in modern-day San Francisco. Keeping their supernatural identities separate and secret from their ordinary lives often becomes a challenge for them, with the exposure of magic having far-reaching consequences on their various relationships and resulting in a number of police and FBI investigations throughout the series. The series initially focuses on the three Halliwell sisters, Prue (Shannen Doherty), Piper (Holly Marie Combs), and Phoebe (Alyssa Milano).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:15:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Jawan - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/jawan-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Jawan (/dʒəwɑːn/ transl. Soldier) is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language vigilante action film co-written and directed by Atlee (in his Hindi film debut).[5] It is produced by Gauri Khan and Gaurav Verma under Red Chillies Entertainment. The film stars Shah Rukh Khan in a dual role as a father and son alongside Nayanthara (in her Hindi film debut) and Vijay Sethupathi. In the film, Azad, the jailer of a woman&amp;#39;s prison and a vigilante who recruits inmates and commits acts that shed light on corruption in India.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 09:03:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fast and Furious Presents - Hobbs and Shaw - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fast-and-furious-presents-hobbs-and-shaw-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest-grossing action films of all time, sci-fi, superhero and fantasy films are not included; see List of highest-grossing science fiction films, List of highest-grossing superhero films and List of highest-grossing fantasy films.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is a list of highest grossing action films of time. The top 3 are along the highest-grossing films, being 11th, 12th and 33rd. James Bond is the most frequent franchise with 11 films on the list. All of the films have had a theatrical run (including re-releases) since 1991, and films that have not played during this period do not appear on the chart because of ticket-price inflation, population size and ticket purchasing trends not being considered. 2015 is the most frequent year with 5 films on the list.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 08:55:56 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>