<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:56:24 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Rautu Ka Raaz - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/rautu-ka-raaz-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Rautu Ka Raaz is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language mystery film directed by Anand Surapur and produced by Zee Studios along with Umesh Kr Bansal, Anand Surapur and Chintu Srivastava. The film stars Nawazuddin Siddiqui, Narayani Shastri, Rajesh Kumar and Atul Tiwari in key roles.[1][2][3] It was featured at the 54th IFFI.[4][5]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;It was released over ZEE5 on 28 June 2024 to positive reviews.[6][7][8][9][10][11]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:53:18 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Valiant One - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/valiant-one-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mark Antony is a 2023 Indian Tamil-language science fiction action comedy film directed by Adhik Ravichandran. The film stars Vishal and S. J. Suryah in dual roles with Ritu Varma, Sunil, Selvaraghavan, Abhinaya, Y. G. Mahendran, Nizhalgal Ravi, Redin Kingsley and Manikandan in supporting roles. In the film, Mark, the son of a gangster Antony, finds a telephone which can contact the past, but Madhan, the son of rival gangster Jackie, wants it for himself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:49:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bayou - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-bayou-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The music for the 2025 period supernatural horror film Sinners written, produced, and directed by Ryan Coogler, consisted of two projects produced by Sony Music. The first album, Sinners (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack), featured various genres performed by blues musicians along with the cast members. The second album, Sinners (Original Motion Picture Score), consisted of the original score composed by Ludwig Göransson, Coogler&amp;#39;s frequent collaborator. Both albums were distributed under the Sony Masterworks and Sony Classical Records labels on April 18, 2025, the same day as the film&amp;#39;s release.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:46:56 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympus Has Fallen - 2013</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/olympus-has-fallen-2013/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Olympus Has Fallen is a 2013 American political action thriller film directed and co-produced by Antoine Fuqua from a screenplay written by Creighton Rothenberger and Katrin Benedikt, and is the first installment in the Has Fallen film series. The film stars Gerard Butler (who also co-produced), Aaron Eckhart, and Morgan Freeman with Angela Bassett, Robert Forster, Cole Hauser, Ashley Judd, Melissa Leo, Dylan McDermott, Radha Mitchell, and Rick Yune in supporting roles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:44:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Free Guy - 2021</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/free-guy-2021/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Respect is a 2021 American biographical musical drama film directed by Liesl Tommy (in her feature directorial debut), written by Tracey Scott Wilson and Callie Khouri, based on the life of American singer Aretha Franklin. The film stars Jennifer Hudson as Franklin, with Forest Whitaker, Marlon Wayans, Audra McDonald, Marc Maron, Tituss Burgess, and Mary J. Blige in supporting roles. The film follows the first three decades of Franklin&amp;#39;s life, from being born as a musical prodigy in an affluent African-American family, the repercussions of losing her mother at age 10 to her arduous rise to international musical stardom, while enduring an abusive marriage, ultimately concluding with the recording of her influential live album Amazing Grace (1972).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 10:40:14 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mission Raniganj - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mission-raniganj-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mission Raniganj: The Great Bharat Rescue is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language disaster thriller film[4] directed by Tinu Suresh Desai and produced by Pooja Entertainment.[5][6] Based on the Raniganj Coalfields collapse of 1989 in West Bengal, the film stars Akshay Kumar and Parineeti Chopra.[7][8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mission Raniganj is based on Jaswant Singh Gill, a brave and diligent mining engineer from IIT Dhanbad who rescued 65 trapped miners at the Raniganj Coalfields in 1989.[9]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:57:19 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Avengers Grimm - 2015</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/avengers-grimm-2015/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Avengers Grimm is a 2015 American superhero film written, co-edited, and directed by Jeremy M. Inman. The film, produced by B-movie film company The Asylum, stars Casper Van Dien, Lou Ferrigno, Kimo Leopoldo, Lauren Parkinson, Milynn Sarley, Marah Fairclough, Rileah Vanderbilt, and Elizabeth Peterson.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film is a mockbuster of the Marvel Studios superhero film Avengers: Age of Ultron and the ABC TV series Once Upon a Time.[2] The film received negative reviews from critics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:47:17 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Aitraaz - 2004</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/aitraaz-2004/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mughal-e-Azam (transl. The Great Mughal) is a 1960 Indian epic historical drama film produced and directed by K. Asif. Starring Prithviraj Kapoor, Dilip Kumar, Madhubala, and Durga Khote, it follows the love affair between Mughal Prince Salim (who went on to become Emperor Jahangir) and Anarkali, a court dancer. Salim&amp;#39;s father, Emperor Akbar, disapproves of the relationship, which leads to a war between father and son.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:43:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Raid 2 - 2014</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-raid-2-2014/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Raid is a 2011 Indonesian action thriller film written and directed by Gareth Evans and produced by Ario Sagantoro.[6] The film stars Iko Uwais, Joe Taslim, Donny Alamsyah, Ray Sahetapy and Yayan Ruhian. The film follows an Indonesian National Police tactical squad that is deployed to raid a ruthless drug lord&amp;#39;s apartment block in the slums of Jakarta, only to be encircled by the criminals, forcing them to fight their way through the complex.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:37:06 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Raid - 2011</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-raid-2011/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Raid is a 2011 Indonesian action thriller film written and directed by Gareth Evans and produced by Ario Sagantoro.[6] The film stars Iko Uwais, Joe Taslim, Donny Alamsyah, Ray Sahetapy and Yayan Ruhian. The film follows an Indonesian National Police tactical squad that is deployed to raid a ruthless drug lord&amp;#39;s apartment block in the slums of Jakarta, only to be encircled by the criminals, forcing them to fight their way through the complex.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:34:44 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Masti Express - 2011</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/masti-express-2011/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Masti Express is a 2011 Indian Hindi-language comedy film directed by Vikram Pradhan and starring Rajpal Yadav, Divya Dutta and Johny Lever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The songs were composed by Chinar–Mahesh. Lyrics by Manoj Yadav.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Taran Adarsh of Bollywood Hungama wrote that &amp;#34;Quite an interesting idea, I must add, but interesting ideas don&amp;#39;t necessarily translate into fascinating cinematic experiences&amp;#34;.[3] Komal Nahta of Koimoi wrote that &amp;#34;On the whole, Masti Express is too dull to impress at the box-office&amp;#34;.[4] A critic from The Times of India wrote that &amp;#34;Funny only in bits and pieces, Masti Express doesn&amp;#39;t live up to its name&amp;#34;.[5] A critic from Webdunia rated the film 2 out of 5.[6] A critic from Movie Talkies wrote that &amp;#34;Unfortunately, the report card for Vikram Pradhan’s directorial debut reads ‘FAIL’. Ultimately, ‘Masti Express’ is a film thoroughly derailed&amp;#34;.[7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:29:21 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Great Grand Masti - 2016</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/great-grand-masti-2016/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Great Grand Masti (transl. Great Grand Fun) is a 2016 Indian Hindi-language sex comedy horror film[3] directed by Indra Kumar.[4] It is the third installment in the Masti (film series) after Masti (2004) and Grand Masti (2013). It is produced by Sameer Nair, Aman Gill, Ashok Thakeria, Markand Adhikari and Anand Pandit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;It features an ensemble cast of Riteish Deshmukh, Vivek Oberoi, Aftab Shivdasani, Shreyas Talpade, Urvashi Rautela, Shraddha Das, Mishti Chakraborty, Pooja Bose and Sanjay Mishra in the pivotal roles.[5] Originally scheduled to release on 22 July 2016, the date was advanced to 15 July 2016 after a pirated copy of the film was reportedly leaked online.[6][7] The censor board made 23 deletions from the film including some dialogue deletions and a complete scene and gave the film an A certificate.[8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:27:04 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Grand Masti - 2013</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/grand-masti-2013/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Masti (English translation: Fun) is a 2004 Indian Hindi-language sex comedy film directed by Indra Kumar, starring Ajay Devgn, Vivek Oberoi, Riteish Deshmukh, Aftab Shivdasani, Lara Dutta, Amrita Rao, Tara Sharma, and Genelia.[3] The film was released in 2004, and received positive responses from critics, and also managed to do well at the box office. The film spawned two sequels, Grand Masti (2013) and Great Grand Masti (2016).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:16:03 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Masti - 2004</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/masti-2004/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Masti (English translation: Fun) is a 2004 Indian Hindi-language sex comedy film directed by Indra Kumar, starring Ajay Devgn, Vivek Oberoi, Riteish Deshmukh, Aftab Shivdasani, Lara Dutta, Amrita Rao, Tara Sharma, and Genelia.[3] The film was released in 2004, and received positive responses from critics, and also managed to do well at the box office. The film spawned two sequels, Grand Masti (2013) and Great Grand Masti (2016).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:11:35 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Kohrra - 2023 Season 1 Complete EP01 - EP06</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/kohrra-2023-season-1-complete-ep01-ep06/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 09:00:59 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Lucky Baskhar - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/lucky-baskhar-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Lucky Baskhar (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) is the soundtrack album to the 2024 Telugu-language period crime drama film of the same name directed by Venky Atluri and produced by Suryadevara Naga Vamsi and Sai Soujanya under Sithara Entertainments, Srikara Studios and Fortune Four Cinemas, starring Dulquer Salmaan and Meenakshi Chaudhary. The album featured three songs composed by G. V. Prakash Kumar with lyrics written by Sri Mani and Ramajogayya Sastry. The album was released under the Aditya Music label on 11 November 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:55:43 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohrey - 2024 Season 1 Complete EP01 - EP08</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mohrey-2024-season-1-complete-ep01-ep08/</link><description>&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-left p-4 mt-4&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:15:58 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Exhuma - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/exhuma-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Shambhala is a 2024 drama film directed by Min Bahadur Bham from a screenplay written by Bham and Abinash Bikram Shah. Starring Thinley Lhamo, Tenzin Dalha and Sonam Topden.[1][2][3] Shambhala is the most expensive movie of Nepal made on the budget रू15 crore (US$1.1 million). It was selected in the Competition at the 74th Berlin International Film Festival, where it competed for the Golden Bear. The film narrates the life trajectory of a Tibetan female refugee who is feeling the brunt in search of her missing husband, a task which she has to do it amidst being pregnant under challenging precarious circumstances.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 08:07:53 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Seal Team Six - The Raid on Osama Bin Laden - 2012</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/seal-team-six-the-raid-on-osama-bin-laden-2012/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;On May 2,[a] 2011, the United States conducted Operation Neptune Spear, in which SEAL Team Six shot and killed Osama bin Laden at his &amp;#34;Waziristan Haveli&amp;#34; in Abbottabad, Pakistan.[1] Bin Laden, who founded al-Qaeda and masterminded the September 11 attacks, had been the subject of a United States military manhunt since the beginning of the War in Afghanistan, but escaped to Pakistan—allegedly with Pakistani support—during or after the Battle of Tora Bora in December 2001. The mission was part of an effort led by the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), with the Joint Special Operations Command (JSOC) coordinating the Special Mission Units involved in the raid. In addition to SEAL Team Six, participating units under JSOC included the 160th Special Operations Aviation Regiment (Airborne) and the CIA&amp;#39;s Special Activities Division, which recruits heavily from among former JSOC Special Mission Units.[2][3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:22:13 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Salaar Part 1 – Ceasefire - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/salaar-part-1-ceasefire-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;This is a list of Indian cinema films released in 2023.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is the list of highest-grossing Indian films released in 2023. The rank of the films in the following table depends on the estimate of worldwide collections as reported by organizations classified as green by Wikipedia.[a] There is no official tracking of domestic box office figures within India.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 07:16:45 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>