<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:14:03 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>The Last Samurai - 2003</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-last-samurai-2003/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Last Samurai (Original Motion Picture Score) is the soundtrack to the 2003 film The Last Samurai directed by Edward Zwick and starring Tom Cruise. The film&amp;#39;s original score is composed and arranged by Hans Zimmer and performed by the Hollywood Studio Symphony under the supervision of conductor and orchestrator Blake Neely. The score was released through Warner Sunset Records on November 25, 2003.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:12:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>The Toys - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/the-toys-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The Amateur is a 2025 American vigilante spy action film directed by James Hawes and written by Ken Nolan and Gary Spinelli. It is based on the 1981 novel of the same name by Robert Littell, which was previously adapted into a 1981 Canadian film. It stars Rami Malek (who also produced), Rachel Brosnahan, Caitríona Balfe, Michael Stuhlbarg, Holt McCallany, Julianne Nicholson, and Laurence Fishburne.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:09:44 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Logout - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/logout-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Logout is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language cyber thriller drama film starring Babil Khan,[1] which is also a sharp critique on our dependence on smartphones.[2] The cast also includes Rasika Dugal, Gandharv Dewan, and Nimisha Nair.[3] Directed by Amit Golani, produced by Viacom18 Studios and Posham Pa Pictures and written by Biswapati Sarkar,[4] Logout explores the dark side of digital fame and the psychological toll of life lived online. It was released on ZEE5 on April 18, 2025.[5]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:00:59 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>14 Days Girlfriend Intlo - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/14-days-girlfriend-intlo-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;14 Days Girlfriend Intlo (transl. 14 days in girlfriend&amp;#39;s house) is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language film comedy written and directed by Sriharsha Manne.[2] The film stars Ankith Koyya, Shriya Kontham, and Vennela Kishore in lead roles.[3][4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released on 7 March 2025.[5]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Harsha (Ankith Koyya) is a young man aspiring to become a filmmaker. He comes across Ahaana&amp;#39;s (Shriya Kontham) profile on a dating app and connects with her. When Ahaana&amp;#39;s parents leave for a wedding, she invites Harsha home. However, what was meant to be a brief visit turns into a 14-day stay.[6]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:55:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Ash - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/ash-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Ash is a 2025 American science fiction horror film directed by Flying Lotus and written by Jonni Remmler. It stars Eiza González, Aaron Paul, Iko Uwais, Kate Elliott, Beulah Koale, and Lotus.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Ash had its world premiere at the SXSW on March 11, 2025, and was released on March 21, 2025. The film has grossed $956,233 and received generally positive reviews from critics, with praise aimed towards the performances, atmosphere, and visuals, as well as Lotus’ direction and score.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:16:15 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>L2: Empuraan - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/l2-empuraan-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Sikandar is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language action drama film written and directed by A. R. Murugadoss and produced by Sajid Nadiadwala. It stars Salman Khan, Rashmika Mandanna, Sathyaraj, Kajal Aggarwal, Sharman Joshi, Prateik Babbar, Kishore, Jatin Sarna and Sanjay Kapoor. In the film, Salman khan plays in titular role as Sanjay &amp;#34;Sikandar&amp;#34; Rajkot. (Khan) is hunted by a politician seeking revenge for a family tragedy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:43:02 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajab Raat Ni Gajab Vaat - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/ajab-raat-ni-gajab-vaat-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Ajab Raat Ni Gajab Vaat is a 2024 Gujarati comedy drama,[1] directed by Prem Gadhavi &amp;amp; Killol Parmar and written by Prem Gadhavi, Aditi Varma &amp;amp; Nikita Shah. It stars Bhavya Gandhi[2] Aarohi Patel,[3][4] Deep Vaidya, Radhika Barot &amp;amp; RJ Harsh. The film is produced by Dr. Jayesh Pavra[5] The film will be distributed by Rupam Entertainment Pvt Ltd&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Kartik, a young YouTuber, is known for conducting loyalty tests on females. His friend Nilay urges him to chalk out an elopement plan for his girlfriend. Things take a complicated turn when they reach the wrong address and a different girl runs away with them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:33:54 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Reva - 2018</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/reva-2018/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Reva: A Journey Within is a 2018 Gujarati adventure drama film starring Chetan Dhanani and Monal Gajjar produced by Brainbox Studios and Baroda Talkies. The film is based on Gujarati author Dhruv Bhatt&amp;#39;s 1998 Gujarati novel Tatvamasi. The film was directed by Rahul Bhole and Vinit Kanojia. It was released on 6 April 2018 to highly positive critic reviews praising performances of cast, story and cinematography and positive commercial acclaim too. The film won the National Film Award for Best Feature Film in Gujarati.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:29:46 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Chaal Jeevi Laiye - 2019</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/chaal-jeevi-laiye-2019/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Chaal Jeevi Laiye! (Gujarati: ચાલ જીવી લઈયે! transl. Come, Let&amp;#39;s Live!) is a 2019 Indian Gujarati-language comedy drama road film written and directed by Vipul Mehta, and produced by Rashmin Majithia under the banner Coconut Motion Pictures. The film stars Siddharth Randeria, Yash Soni, and Aarohi Patel.[3] The soundtrack was composed by Sachin–Jigar.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released in India on 1 February 2019.[5] and had completed its 300 weeks in cinemas on 25th October 2024. It became the highest-grossing film of Gujarati cinema, grossing over est. ₹52.14 crore (US$6.1 million)[1] and the first film released in this century to enter its 7th year in theatres. It is remade in Marathi as Ole Aale (2024), starring Nana Patekar[6] in the lead.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:17:50 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Crazxy- 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/crazxy-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Crazxy is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language thriller film written and directed by Girish Kohli in his directorial debut and produced by Sohum Shah, Mukesh Shah, Amita Shah and Adesh Prasad and co-produced by Ankit Jain under Sohum Shah Films. The film stars Sohum in the lead role and the only on-screen character, as surgeon Abhimanyu Sood, who races against time to rescue his daughter from a kidnapper.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:09:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Superboys of Malegaon - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/superboys-of-malegaon-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Superboys of Malegaon is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language coming-of-age drama film directed by Reema Kagti and written by Varun Grover. Inspired by the 2008 documentary Supermen of Malegaon, it is based on the life of Nasir Shaikh and other amateur filmmakers in the small town of Malegaon.[1][5][6] The film stars Adarsh Gourav, Vineet Kumar Singh, Shashank Arora, and Anuj Singh Duhan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film premiered at the 2024 Toronto International Film Festival on 13 September 2024. It was theatrically released on 28 February 2025, and received positive reviews from critics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:05:13 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Officer on Duty - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/officer-on-duty-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Officer on Duty is a 2025 Indian Malayalam-language crime action thriller film directed by Jithu Ashraf (in his directorial debut) and written by Shahi Kabir.[3] It stars Kunchacko Boban, Vishak Nair, Jagadish and Priyamani. The film was positively received by critics and audiences, with its performances (particularly by Kunchacko Boban, Jagadish and Vishak Nair), story, and music garnering praise and turned out to be commercial success.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:01:34 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Barroz - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/barroz-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Marco is a 2024 Indian Malayalam-language neo-noir action thriller film written and directed by Haneef Adeni and produced by Shareef Muhammed under his Cubes Entertainments banner. The film stars Unni Mukundan in the titular role, alongside Siddique, Jagadish, Kabir Duhan Singh, Abhimanyu Shammi Thilakan, Anson Paul, Ishaan Shoukath and Yukti Thareja in supporting roles. The film is a standalone spin-off to Mikhael. Some of the characters from Mikhael are placed in a different story but in the same universe as Mikhael.[5][6] The plot follows Marco Jr, a ruthless gangster and the adopted son of the Adattu crime family, who goes on a bloody rampage after the brutal death of his blind foster brother Victor.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:54:12 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Agent - 2023</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/agent-2023/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Agent Vinod is a 2012 Indian Hindi-language neo-noir action spy film written and directed by Sriram Raghavan and produced by Saif Ali Khan and Dinesh Vijan. An adaptation of the 1977 film of the same name, the film revolves around terrorist conspiracy and stars Khan and Kareena Kapoor in the lead roles, while Ram Kapoor, Prem Chopra, Shahbaz Khan and Adil Hussain appear in prominent roles with Ravi Kishan in a special appearance.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:45:18 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Operation Raavan - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/operation-raavan-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Operation Raavan is a 2024 Indian Telugu-language crime thriller film written and directed by Venkata Satya.[1] The film features Rakshit Atluri and Sangeerthana Vipin in lead roles. Operation Raavan was released on 26 July 2024.[2][3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The story revolves around a young journalist Anand Sriram, who works at TV45 under Aamani, a senior journalist. While Aamani is struggling to expose the corruption of a minister, they encounter mysterious murders of brides-to-be. As police fails to solve the case, Anand and Aamani start the investigation, discovering clues and finding Jeevitha at the heart of the mystery.[citation needed]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:40:37 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Hisaab Barabar - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/hisaab-barabar-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Hisaab Barabar is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language satirical thriller film written and directed by Ashwni Dhir.[2] The film stars R. Madhavan in the lead role,[3] with Neil Nitin Mukesh, Kirti Kulhari,[4][5] Rashami Desai, and Faisal Rashid in supporting roles.[2][6][7] The story follows a railway ticket checker who uncovers discrepancies in minor bank transactions, which leads him to uncover deeper systemic corruption.[8][9] The film is produced by Jio Studios and SP Cinecorp. The film premiered at the 55th International Film Festival of India in Goa on 26 November 2024 and was released on 24 January 2025 on ZEE5.[2][10][11]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:25:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Viduthalai Part 2 - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/viduthalai-part-2-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Viduthalai Part 2 (transl. Liberation Part 2) is a 2024 Indian Tamil-language period political crime thriller film directed and co-produced by Vetrimaaran under RS Infotainment and Grass Root Film Company. It is the direct sequel to Viduthalai Part 1 (2023) and the second of a two-part adaptation of Jeyamohan&amp;#39;s short story Thunaivan (transl. Companion). It follows the travels of a police constable amidst an operation to apprehend a revolutionary. Vijay Sethupathi, Soori, Gautham Vasudev Menon, Bhavani Sre, Rajiv Menon, Ilavarasu, Balaji Sakthivel, Saravana Subbiah, Chetan and Munnar Ramesh reprise their roles from the first film, with Manju Warrier, Kishore, Anurag Kashyap, Bose Venkat, Vincent Asokan and Ken Karunas joining the ensemble cast.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:12:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Sabdham - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/sabdham-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Sabdham (transl. Sound) is an 2025 Indian Tamil-language horror thriller film written and directed by Arivazhagan Venkatachalam. The film is jointly produced by Siva and S. Banupriya Siva under 7G Films and AAlpha Frames and stars Aadhi Pinisetty and Lakshmi Menon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was announced in December 2022, along with the title of the film. Principal photography commenced the same month in Munnar along with a schedule in Chennai later in Mumbai and wrapped by late-September 2023. The film has music composed by S. Thaman, cinematography handled by Arun Bathmanaban and editing by V. J. Sabu Joseph.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:41:57 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Court State vs A Nobody - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/court-state-vs-a-nobody-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Court – State vs. A Nobody is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language legal drama film written and directed by Ram Jagadeesh in his directorial debut; it was produced by Prashanti Tipirneni and presented by Nani, under Wall Poster Cinema.[3][4] The film stars Priyadarshi Pulikonda, Harsh Roshan, Sridevi, and Sivaji alongside, P. Sai Kumar, Harsha Vardhan, Rohini, Subhalekha Sudhakar, Surabhi Prabhavathi, and Rajasekhar Aningi.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released on 14 March 2025 to positive reviews from critics and was successful at the box office grossing ₹48.75 crore worldwide.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:39:21 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Raduaa - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/raduaa-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Raduaa is an Indian Punjabi science fiction film directed by and starring Nav Bajwa with Gurpreet Ghuggi and Satinder Satti. The film&amp;#39;s plot is based upon a scientific experiment which unexpectedly results in time travel from the present day to 1955. The film was released on 11 May 2018.[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Raduaa Returns, a sequel released on 2024.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;It is a comedy science fiction movie where four people living in 2018 travel back in time to 1955. Nav (Nav Bajwa) – an IT expert, Sukhi (Gurpreet Ghuggi) – a mechanic, and Hem Chand Lamba (B. N. Sharma) – a lab technician, are living as tenants in Chandigarh. Their landlady is Jasmeen (Satinder Satti). Sukhi and Hem Chand do not pay rent regularly; she warns them either to pay rent or vacate. Nav has invented a machine which he calls Raduaa and earns money with it.[how?] Sukhi&amp;#39;s relationship with his wife, who had high dreams, is strained. She leaves him along with her son and asks him to pay 15 lacs if he want to meet his son. Sukhi tries to steal the money but is caught. Nav and Hem Chand try to help him by intercepting a call of drug dealers through his Raduaa. The three impersonate drug dealers and go to an agreed location for the deal, but the police arrive and the three of them are caught. However, when the police find that they are not carrying drugs, they are released. Nav thinks that someone is hearing their calls and thinks that Raduaa is not working properly. While trying to repair it, Jasmeen comes. In the commotion Hem Chand accidentally throws the beaker, containing a green chemical; there are electric shocks and the four travel back to 1955 where they appear in a village. The villagers look at them with suspicion. The sarpanch of the village gives them refuge and they work together to return to 2018. Whether they succeed in returning or something more mysterious is in wait is to be seen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:35:15 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>