<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Movies Manias</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/</link><description/><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:51:05 UTC</lastBuildDate><item><title>Hisaab Barabar - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/hisaab-barabar-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Hisaab Barabar is a 2024 Indian Hindi-language satirical thriller film written and directed by Ashwni Dhir.[2] The film stars R. Madhavan in the lead role,[3] with Neil Nitin Mukesh, Kirti Kulhari,[4][5] Rashami Desai, and Faisal Rashid in supporting roles.[2][6][7] The story follows a railway ticket checker who uncovers discrepancies in minor bank transactions, which leads him to uncover deeper systemic corruption.[8][9] The film is produced by Jio Studios and SP Cinecorp. The film premiered at the 55th International Film Festival of India in Goa on 26 November 2024 and was released on 24 January 2025 on ZEE5.[2][10][11]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:25:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Viduthalai Part 2 - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/viduthalai-part-2-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Viduthalai Part 2 (transl. Liberation Part 2) is a 2024 Indian Tamil-language period political crime thriller film directed and co-produced by Vetrimaaran under RS Infotainment and Grass Root Film Company. It is the direct sequel to Viduthalai Part 1 (2023) and the second of a two-part adaptation of Jeyamohan&amp;#39;s short story Thunaivan (transl. Companion). It follows the travels of a police constable amidst an operation to apprehend a revolutionary. Vijay Sethupathi, Soori, Gautham Vasudev Menon, Bhavani Sre, Rajiv Menon, Ilavarasu, Balaji Sakthivel, Saravana Subbiah, Chetan and Munnar Ramesh reprise their roles from the first film, with Manju Warrier, Kishore, Anurag Kashyap, Bose Venkat, Vincent Asokan and Ken Karunas joining the ensemble cast.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:12:11 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Sabdham - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/sabdham-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Sabdham (transl. Sound) is an 2025 Indian Tamil-language horror thriller film written and directed by Arivazhagan Venkatachalam. The film is jointly produced by Siva and S. Banupriya Siva under 7G Films and AAlpha Frames and stars Aadhi Pinisetty and Lakshmi Menon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was announced in December 2022, along with the title of the film. Principal photography commenced the same month in Munnar along with a schedule in Chennai later in Mumbai and wrapped by late-September 2023. The film has music composed by S. Thaman, cinematography handled by Arun Bathmanaban and editing by V. J. Sabu Joseph.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:41:57 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Court State vs A Nobody - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/court-state-vs-a-nobody-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Court – State vs. A Nobody is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language legal drama film written and directed by Ram Jagadeesh in his directorial debut; it was produced by Prashanti Tipirneni and presented by Nani, under Wall Poster Cinema.[3][4] The film stars Priyadarshi Pulikonda, Harsh Roshan, Sridevi, and Sivaji alongside, P. Sai Kumar, Harsha Vardhan, Rohini, Subhalekha Sudhakar, Surabhi Prabhavathi, and Rajasekhar Aningi.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released on 14 March 2025 to positive reviews from critics and was successful at the box office grossing ₹48.75 crore worldwide.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:39:21 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Raduaa - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/raduaa-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Raduaa is an Indian Punjabi science fiction film directed by and starring Nav Bajwa with Gurpreet Ghuggi and Satinder Satti. The film&amp;#39;s plot is based upon a scientific experiment which unexpectedly results in time travel from the present day to 1955. The film was released on 11 May 2018.[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Raduaa Returns, a sequel released on 2024.[2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;It is a comedy science fiction movie where four people living in 2018 travel back in time to 1955. Nav (Nav Bajwa) – an IT expert, Sukhi (Gurpreet Ghuggi) – a mechanic, and Hem Chand Lamba (B. N. Sharma) – a lab technician, are living as tenants in Chandigarh. Their landlady is Jasmeen (Satinder Satti). Sukhi and Hem Chand do not pay rent regularly; she warns them either to pay rent or vacate. Nav has invented a machine which he calls Raduaa and earns money with it.[how?] Sukhi&amp;#39;s relationship with his wife, who had high dreams, is strained. She leaves him along with her son and asks him to pay 15 lacs if he want to meet his son. Sukhi tries to steal the money but is caught. Nav and Hem Chand try to help him by intercepting a call of drug dealers through his Raduaa. The three impersonate drug dealers and go to an agreed location for the deal, but the police arrive and the three of them are caught. However, when the police find that they are not carrying drugs, they are released. Nav thinks that someone is hearing their calls and thinks that Raduaa is not working properly. While trying to repair it, Jasmeen comes. In the commotion Hem Chand accidentally throws the beaker, containing a green chemical; there are electric shocks and the four travel back to 1955 where they appear in a village. The villagers look at them with suspicion. The sarpanch of the village gives them refuge and they work together to return to 2018. Whether they succeed in returning or something more mysterious is in wait is to be seen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:35:15 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Majhail - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/majhail-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Majhail is a Punjabi-language action film directed by Dheeraj Kedarnath Rattan.[1][2][3] The film is written by Dheeraj Kedarnath Rattan and Manila Rattan.[4] It stars Dev Kharoud and Roopi Gill in lead roles and Guggu Gill, Dheeraj Kumar, Vadda Grewal, and Hobby Dhaliwal in supporting roles.[5][6] The film released in theatres on 31 January 2025.[7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was filmed at multiple locations across Punjab, including Nabha, Mohali, Kurali, Morinda, and Nandpur Kalaur.[1] Principal photography for the film commenced on 14 May 2024 and concluded in September 2024.[8][9][10]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:25:34 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Gumasthan - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/gumasthan-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Gumasthan (transl. Clerk) is a is 2024 Indian Malayalam-language thriller film directed by Amal K. Joby.[1][2]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The cunning clerk, who knows every loop hole in law and court, kills his wife. But when the public and police come to know about the murder, they try to prove him guilty. But for that they have to bypass his intelligence. The story revolves around the hidden mysteries of the clerk and his house.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:20:08 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mere Husband Ki Biwi - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mere-husband-ki-biwi-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mere Husband Ki Biwi (transl. My husband&amp;#39;s wife), is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language romantic comedy film written and directed by Mudassar Aziz and produced by Vashu Bhagnani, Jackky Bhagnani and Deepshikha Deshmukh under their banner Pooja Entertainment.[3] The film stars Arjun Kapoor, Bhumi Pednekar and Rakul Preet Singh in lead roles.[4] The film was released on 21 February 2025.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Ankur Chadda (Arjun Kapoor) is in real estate business with his father (Shakti Kapoor) and is still having nightmares 5 years after his divorce with his college love Prabhleen Kaur Dhillon (Bhumi Pednekar). As a result he is unable to sustain any relationship. He goes to Rishikesh to finalize a real estate deal where he meets Antara Khanna (Rakul Preet Singh), whom he knows from college. Upon advice of his best friend Rehan Qureshi (Harsh Gujral) he pursues a relationship with Antara and both hit it off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:44:47 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikandar - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/sikandar-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Sikandar is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language action drama film written and directed by A. R. Murugadoss and produced by Sajid Nadiadwala. It stars Salman Khan, Rashmika Mandanna, Sathyaraj, Kajal Aggarwal, Sharman Joshi, Prateik Babbar, Kishore, Jatin Sarna and Sanjay Kapoor. In the film, Salman khan plays in titular role as Sanjay &amp;#34;Sikandar&amp;#34; Rajkot. (Khan) is hunted by a politician seeking revenge for a family tragedy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:40:31 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanguva - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/kanguva-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Maharaja (transl. The Great King)[b] is a 2024 Indian Tamil-language action thriller film[6] directed by Nithilan Saminathan. It is jointly produced by The Route, Think Studios and Passion Studios. The film stars Vijay Sethupathi, alongside Anurag Kashyap, Mamta Mohandas, Natty Subramaniam, Abhirami, Divyabharathi, Singampuli, Aruldoss, Munishkanth, Sachana Namidass, Manikandan and Bharathiraja. It follows a barber in Chennai who goes to the police station to retrieve his stolen dustbin, only for the police to find his intentions to be something else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:35:49 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Gandhi 3 - 2024</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/gandhi-3-2024/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Agni is an 2024 Indian Hindi-language action thriller written and directed by Rahul Dholakia.[1] The film is produced by Ritesh Sidhwani and Farhan Akhtar under Excel Entertainment in association with Amazon MGM Studios and stars Pratik Gandhi, Divyenndu, Jitendra Joshi, Saiyami Kher and Kabir Shah in lead roles.[2][3] Agni was released on 6 December 2024 on Amazon Prime Video to positive reviews.[4][5][6][7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;In a city plagued by an unexplained rise in fires, Vithal, a brave firefighter, reluctantly teams up with his brother-in-law, Samit, a skilled but stubborn policeman, to get to the bottom of the escalating crisis. As tensions mount and time runs short, the two must put aside their personal differences to solve the mystery and shield Mumbai from looming catastrophe.[8]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:31:54 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Chhorii 2 - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/chhorii-2-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Chhorii 2 (transl. Girl 2) is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language horror film directed by Vishal Furia and produced by Bhushan Kumar, Krishan Kumar, Vikram Malhotra and Jack Davis.[2][3] A sequel to Chhorii (2021), the film features Nushrratt Bharuccha in the lead role, alongside Soha Ali Khan, Gashmeer Mahajani and Saurabh Goyal.[4][5][6] The film was premiered on Amazon Prime Video on 11 April 2025.[7]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The principal photography started on 30 November 2022.[8] The film was wrapped up on 8 February 2023.[9]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:27:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Fikar Karo-Na - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/fikar-karo-na-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Asha Bhosle is an Indian playback singer who has been cited by the Guinness Book of World Records as the most recorded singer in history.[1]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;| &amp;#34;Maang Ke Saath Tumhaara&amp;#34; -&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;| &amp;#34;Main Chali, Main Chali&amp;#34; -&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:21:45 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Deva - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/deva-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Deva is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language action thriller film directed by Rosshan Andrrews, and produced by Siddharth Roy Kapur under Roy Kapur Films. The film stars Shahid Kapoor, Pooja Hegde and Pavail Gulati. It is a remake of Andrrews&amp;#39;s own 2013 Malayalam film Mumbai Police, with a different climax.[5] The film follows a violent cop who undergoes a personality change after losing his memory in an accident and has to reinvestigate the murder of a fellow police officer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:16:16 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Umbarro- 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/umbarro-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Umbarro is a 2025 Gujarati family comedy drama film directed by Abhishek Shah. It stars Vandana Pathak, Kaajal Oza Vaidya, Suchita Trivedi, Deeksha Joshi, Tarjanee Bhadla, Tejal Panchasara, Vineeta Joshee, Aarjav Trivedi, and Galsar Sanjay in a lead role.[3] The film is a remake of 2021 Marathi film Jhimma.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Seven women from rural Gujarat embark on their first international trip to London, facing cultural clashes, language barriers, and societal stigmas along their journey to claim their space in the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:59:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuk-tuk - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/tuk-tuk-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Tuk Tuk is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language supernatural comedy film[1] written and directed by Supreeth C Krishna, produced by Rahul Reddy D, Lokku Sri Varun, C Sree Ramulu Reddy under the banners of Chitravaahani Producions and RYG Cinemas[2] The film features Harsh Roshan, Karthikeya Dev, Madhu Sudhan Rapeti, Saanve Megghana and Nihal Kodhaty in important roles.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;In a rural village of Chittoor, three aimless young men, desperate to earn money, resort to secretly recording women bathing. Their lives take a strange turn when they come across a scooter possessed by a spirit. Seizing the opportunity, they use the scooter to lead a Ganesh Chaturthi procession and start making money. However, their world is turned upside down when they discover the spirit is actually a girl. The rest of the story unravels the mystery of how the girl became a spirit, how she ended up in the scooter, and the tragic love story that led to her untimely fate.[4]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:55:32 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Mad Square - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/mad-square-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Mad Square (stylized as MAD²) is a 2025 Indian Telugu-language action comedy film written and directed by Kalyan Shankar and produced by Haarika Suryadevara and S. Naga Vamsi. A sequel to the 2023 film Mad, the film has an ensemble cast of Narne Nithiin, Sangeeth Sobhan, Ram Nitin and Priyanka Jawalkar.[3]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The film was released on 28 March 2025[4][5] to mixed reviews from critics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:51:41 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Ash - 2025 ( Hindi-English )</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/ash-2025-hindi-english/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;This is a list of Hindi cinema films released in 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;The following is the list of highest-grossing Hindi cinema films released in 2024.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full bg-gray-800 text-gray-300 text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;
Tags:
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:46:17 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Emergency - 2025</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/emergency-2025/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Emergency is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language historical biographical drama film[7] directed and co-produced by Kangana Ranaut, based on a screenplay by Ritesh Shah and story written by Ranaut.[8] Based on the Indian Emergency, it stars Ranaut as former Prime Minister of India, Indira Gandhi.[9][10]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Principal photography commenced in July 2022 and ended in January 2023.[11] It was originally scheduled for release on 6 September 2024, but was postponed due to pending certification of the Central Board of Film Certification.[12][13] Later, it was cleared by CBFC and released on 17 January 2025 to negative reviews from film critics.[14][15][16] The film also emerged as a box-office flop.[17][18][19]&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:06:09 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Nadaaniyan</title><link>https://movies.technologymanias.com/nadaaniyan/</link><description>&amp;lt;p class=&amp;#34;w-full text-white text-justify py-2 mt-4 px-4 overflow-auto break-words&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Nadaaniyan (transl. Innocence) is a 2025 Indian Hindi-language teen romantic comedy film directed by Shauna Gautam (in her directorial debut) and produced by Karan Johar, Apoorva Mehta and Somen Mishra under Dharmatic Entertainment. The film stars Ibrahim Ali Khan (in his acting debut) and Khushi Kapoor, alongside Mahima Chaudhry, Dia Mirza, Suniel Shetty, and Jugal Hansraj. It tells the story of a privileged South Delhi school girl who gets a boyfriend-for-hire to get back at her family and classmates.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:31:49 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>